export const exercise1 =[
	{
	question:1,
	exercise : "You learn French ?",
	answer:"Apprenez-vous.",
	subquestion:"Français"
},
{
	question:2,
	exercise : "Today is  special",
	answer:"Aujourd’hui est",
	subquestion:"Special"
},
{
	question:3,
	exercise : "You are learning French.",
	answer:"Vous apprenez",
	subquestion:"le Français"
},
{
	question:4,
	exercise : "Good morning  and good luck",
	answer:"Bonjour",
	subquestion:"et bonne chance."
},
{
	question:5,
	exercise : "Enjoy yourself",
	answer:"soyez ",
	subquestion:"attentif"
}
]
export const exercise2 = [
	{
	question:1,
	exercise:"Are You Learning French? yes",
	answer:"Apprenez-vous  ",
	subquestion:"Français? Oui"

	},

	{
	question:2,
	exercise:"Good evening, are you alone?",
	answer:"bonsoir!  ",
	subquestion:"êtes vous  seul?"

	},

	{
	question:3,
	exercise:"Yes, a room is free.Oui",
	answer:"une chambre  ",
	subquestion:"est libre"
	},
	{
		question:4,
		exercise:"Blessing is alone Blessing EST  ",
		answer:"Seul",
		subquestion:""
	},

	{
		question:5,
		exercise:"It cost £ 50",
		answer:". Ça fait",
		subquestion:"£ 50"
	},
 ]

